export const chapter = "Chapter - 20: Unseen Comprehension";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What happened when the boy set out for school?",
          optionA: "He encountered a downpour",
          optionB: "He reached school late",
          optionC: "He enjoyed cycling in the rain",
          correctAnswer: "He encountered a downpour",
        },
        {
          question: "What did the principal declare?",
          optionA: "School assembly was to be held",
          optionB: "It was a holiday",
          optionC: "Extra classes were scheduled",
          correctAnswer: "It was a holiday",
        },
        {
          question: "Why did the boy sit near the window?",
          optionA: "To watch TV",
          optionB: "To look out at the rain",
          optionC: "To play with friends",
          correctAnswer: "To look out at the rain",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Choose and fill in the blanks: (a) If we go out on a rainy day, we may be ____ _ (b) When it rains mildly, it is called a ____ _",
          optionA: "drenched, drizzle",
          optionB: "sweating, storm",
          optionC: "wet, flood",
          correctAnswer: "drenched, drizzle",
        },
        {
          question: "What are the different types of animals?",
          optionA: "Domestic and wild",
          optionB: "Herbivores and carnivores",
          optionC: "Mammals and reptiles",
          correctAnswer: "Domestic and wild",
        },
        {
          question: "Why does man kill animals and what is his sport?",
          optionA: "For fun and hunting",
          optionB: "For food and protection",
          optionC: "For study and research",
          correctAnswer: "For fun and hunting",
        },
        {
          question: "What is our moral duty for animals?",
          optionA: "To exploit them",
          optionB: "To protect and preserve them",
          optionC: "To ignore them",
          correctAnswer: "To protect and preserve them",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Fill in the blanks: (a) Birds and beasts are a _____ part of the environment. (b) Love for animals is a feeling. (c) Cruelty to animals is a offence",
          optionA: "vital, noble, punishable",
          optionB: "significant, kind, permissible",
          optionC: "crucial, good, illegal",
          correctAnswer: "vital, noble, punishable",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the man strive for?",
          optionA: "Wealth",
          optionB: "Knowledge",
          optionC: "Fame",
          correctAnswer: "Knowledge",
        },
        {
          question: "Why does the man go out of his known bounds?",
          optionA: "To escape from life",
          optionB: "To expand his mental horizon",
          optionC: "To visit unknown worlds",
          correctAnswer: "To expand his mental horizon",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "1. Nature manifests its beauty in different shades, and a rainy day is the occasion when the nature is at its ________.",
          options: ["a) worst", "b) brightest", "c) best"],
          correctAnswer: "c) best",
        },
        {
          question:
            "2. Looking at the wet and fresh trees and puddles full of water, I reached back home. I took a bath in order to wash away all the mud that I had taken on the ________.",
          options: ["a) journey", "b) way", "c) road"],
          correctAnswer: "b) way",
        },
        {
          question:
            "3. Some of them live and loiter in dense forests, far away from human habitation. Practically, they do us no _______.",
          options: ["a) help", "b) harm", "c) service"],
          correctAnswer: "b) harm",
        },
        {
          question:
            "4. Practically, they do us no harm. We should love and take care of them. In fact, love for animals is a _______ feeling.",
          options: ["a) noble", "b) selfish", "c) humble"],
          correctAnswer: "a) noble",
        },
        {
          question:
            "5. Birds and beasts are a _______ part of the environment.",
          options: ["a) significant", "b) vital", "c) irrelevant"],
          correctAnswer: "b) vital",
        },
        {
          question:
            "6. Today travelling involves fewer hazards due to fabulous progress in the field of _______.",
          options: ["a) exploration", "b) adventure", "c) communication"],
          correctAnswer: "c) communication",
        },
        {
          question:
            "7. Games and sports help us have a fit body. They give us rest and respite from the dull _______ of daily work.",
          options: ["a) enjoyment", "b) excitement", "c) drudgery"],
          correctAnswer: "c) drudgery",
        },
        {
          question:
            "8. In addition to making a man healthy, playing games helps to inculcate qualities of head and heart. It teaches team spirit, leadership qualities, cooperation, coordination, organisational skills among many other _______.",
          options: ["a) traits", "b) habits", "c) attributes"],
          correctAnswer: "a) traits",
        },
        {
          question:
            "9. A true patriot, in his words and works, must reflect the true spirit of patriotism, that is, selfless love for his _______.",
          options: ["a) nation", "b) family", "c) religion"],
          correctAnswer: "a) nation",
        },
        {
          question:
            "10. The men in Army are called soldiers, those in Navy are called seamen and those in Air Force are called _______.",
          options: ["a) aviators", "b) pilots", "c) airmen"],
          correctAnswer: "c) airmen",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Word formation involves the creation of new words.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Verbs can change to nouns by adding a prefix.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adjectives can change to adverbs by adding a suffix.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A compound word is formed by joining two or more words together.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Suffixes are added at the beginning of a word.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Patriotism means hatred for one's own country.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Travelling helps in expanding mental horizon.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Games and sports have no impact on mental and emotional well-being.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "A prefix is added at the end of a word.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The moon revolves round the earth.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
